http://www.recticel.com/who-we-are/discover-the-recticel-group/privacy-statements/website-privacy-notice.html

Scope
You are visiting the website of Recticel NV/SA, registered in Belgium at Bourgetlaan 42 Avenue du Bourget, 1130 Brussels, registered under number 0405666668 (further: “Recticel”).
By visiting this website, you acknowledge that you have read and understood this privacy notice.
This notice concerns personal data which Recticel collects and uses.
Recticel is committed to comply with all applicable data protection laws and regulations. Below, we provide in a nutshell what this means for you.
Below, we provide in a nutshell what this means for you.
Recticel may collect your personal data
Personal data are data which allow us to identify you as an individual, like your name, address, phone number. On the other hand, anonymized data are not personal data because they do not identify you, for example: statistics regarding the number of visitors to our webpages.
You can visit our website without providing any personal data.
Recticel uses your personal data
We limit our processing of personal information to what is necessary for the intended purpose (eg. to fulfill our contractual obligations towards you, to comply with legal obligations…) or for the purpose for which you provided consent (eg. receiving a newsletter, providing you with information you requested…). We do not collect sensitive personal information (as defined by EU Regulation 2016/679) from you without first obtaining your explicit consent.
We may share your information:
With selected business partners, but only after you have explicitly provided your consent.
With external service providers who perform certain services on Recticel’s behalf, such as an agency which will deliver your order to your address or which sends out newsletters for us.
We may transfer your data to a Recticel entity or a third party established outside of the EEA. If we do, we implement personal data transfer agreements based on the standard clauses published by the European Commission to protect your personal data.
Your Rights
If you are a resident in the European Economic Area, you have the right to: (a) access your personal data; (b) request rectification of your personal data; (c) request portability of your personal data; (d) request restriction of processing of your personal data; (e) object to the processing of your personal data; (f) request erasure of your personal data; (g) request cancellation of your personal data; and (h) if you have provided your consent to the processing of your personal data, you have the right to withdraw your consent at any time.
If you are a resident in France, you have the additional right to make general or specific arrangements for the storage and communications of you personal data after your death.
To exercise any of your rights, please contact us as set out below in the “Contact” section.
Recticel preserves your data
We will keep and process your personal data for as long as reasonably necessary for the purposes for which we received your personal data, taking into account our possible legal and contractual obligations towards you.
If the legal basis for processing is your explicit consent, we will keep and process your personal data for a maximum period of 2 (two) years. When we provide you the opportunity to unsubscribe, and you choose not to, the period of 2 (two) years is calculated from the date we offered you to unsubscribe.
During the time that we keep your personal data, we will take the technical and organizational measures to ensure an appropriate level of security to protect them.
Links to Third-Party Sites and Social Media
Recticel sites may include links to third party sites. When you use these links, you leave our website. Recticel shall not be held liable for the data processing via a third party site. We encourage you to read the privacy policy of every site you visit.
Recticel uses cookies. What does this entail ?
What is a Cookie?
A cookie is a small file that a website asks your browser to store on your computer or mobile device. The cookie allows the website to "remember" your actions or preferences over time. It helps to navigate from page to page on a website, provide secure connections, and remembers preferences from a previous visit, when you return.
Below, we explain the function of the different types of cookies you will encounter on our website.
You will find more information regarding cookies on http://ec.europa.eu/ipg/basics/legal/cookies/index_en.htm.
Cookies On Our Website
Operational cookies: Recticel uses operational cookies. These are small files placed on your computer or device to help you navigate from page to page on the Recticel website. For example, without such cookies, you would need to provide your language preference every time you switch to a different page on the Recticel website. These cookies are thus essential for easy use of the site.
Non-Operational Cookies: We also use cookies to provide other services or to help us improve our products and services. Some cookies provide us statistics about the number of visitors and the web pages viewed. This information helps us to design more useful content for you. Some of these cookies are third party cookies.
Third Party Cookies: We sometimes use third party cookies, like for Google Analytics (__utma, __utmb, __utmc, __utmz, __utmv) or for Youtube (embedded videos : PREF, VISITOR_INFO1_LIVE, YSC). These are non-operational cookies. If we use them, we will inform you of the purpose of the third party cookies and request your consent to store them.
If we use non-operational cookies, we will request whether you accept our use of cookies. If you do not accept such cookies, some services and functionalities do not work. In particular, this may limit your use of the site and its various features, and reduces our ability to improve our products and services and provide engaging content.
How can you manage the cookies?
Most browsers support cookies, but you can set your browsers to decline them and can delete them whenever you like. You can manage the cookies yourself by adapting your preferences in your browser. The exact process depends on which browser you are using, which can be easily found via your search function on internet.
Google Analytics
This website uses Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. ("Google"). Google Analytics uses non-operational cookies, which are text files placed on your computer to help the website analyse how visitors use the site. The information generated by the cookie about your use of the website (including your IP address) will be transmitted to and stored by Google on servers in the United States . At the request of Recticel, Google will use this information for the purpose of evaluating how the website is used, compiling reports on website activity for website operators and providing other services relating to website activity and internet usage. Google may also transfer this information to third parties where required to do so by law, or where such third parties process the information on Google's behalf.
Google will not associate your IP address with any other data held by Google. The IP-anonymisation is active on this website. This means that your IP address is truncated within the area of Member States of the European Union or other parties to the Agreement on the European Economic Area. Only in exceptional cases the whole IP address will be first transferred to a Google server in the USA and truncated there.
You may refuse the use of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings on your browser. Please note though that if you do this you may not be able to use the full functionality of this website.
By using this website, you consent to the processing of data about you by Google in the manner and for the purposes set out above.
You can also opt-out from being tracked by Google Analytics with effect for the future by downloading and installing Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Addon for your current web browser: https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout.
Contact
If you have any questions regarding this website or how we respect your right to privacy, please contact us via mail to Recticel NV/SA - Privacy desk, Bourgetlaan 42 Avenue du Bourget, 1130 Brussels, or via email to dataprotection@recticel.com.
If you do not receive an adequate answer from us, you have the possibility to file a complaint to one of the national supervisory data protection authorities, of which you will find the contact details here: http://ec.europa.eu/justice/data-protection/article-29/structure/data-protection-authorities/index_en.htm
Can we help you?
We are here to assist you! Just click the button below, fill in the contact form and we will get back to you as soon as possible.
Yes, I need more information
Privacy notice - Terms of use Sitemap - Impressum
We use cookies to ensure that we give you the best experience on our website. These cookies perform functions like recognizing you each time you visit the site or helping our team to understand which parts of the site you find most interesting and useful. You can read more about the cookies that we use and their purposes.
Accept
More info
You are now leaving the Recticel website
We do not control the destination site and cannot accept any responsibility for its contents, links, or offers.
I agree
Welcome to the website of Recticel
Recticel Cookie Statement
Recticel uses cookies to make your browsing experience easier and more enjoyable and to better match the content of its websites and apps to your needs and preferences. You can choose to block cookies, but some of our websites and (mobile) applications may not work optimally without them. By clicking 'Accept', you explicitly consent to the use of cookies in accordance with this cookie statement. You can revoke your permission at any time by adjusting your cookie settings in your browser.
For more information see the Recticel Privacy Notice, which contains information about your rights if your personal data, including use of cookies, is processed.
Decline
Accept
Can we help you?
We are here to assist you! Just fill in the contact form below and we will get back to you as soon as possible.
We care about your privacy. That's why we will only use your data to reply to your enquiry. Find out more in our privacy notice to job applicants.
At any moment, you can access, modify or have erased your personal data by sending a request to dataprotection@recticel.com
* indicates a required field
First name
Last name
Country
CountryAfghanistanAlbaniaAlgeriaAmerican SamoaAndorraAngolaAnguillaAntarcticaAntigua and BarbudaArgentinaArmeniaArubaAscension IslandAustraliaAustriaAzerbaijanBahamasBahrainBangladeshBarbadosBelarusBelgiumBelizeBeninBermudaBhutanBoliviaBosnia and HerzegovinaBotswanaBouvet IslandBrazilBritish Indian Ocean TerritoryBritish Virgin IslandsBruneiBulgariaBurkina FasoBurundiCambodiaCameroonCanadaCanary IslandsCape VerdeCaribbean NetherlandsCayman IslandsCentral African RepublicCeuta and MelillaChadChileChinaChristmas IslandClipperton IslandCocos [Keeling] IslandsColombiaComorosCongo - BrazzavilleCongo - KinshasaCook IslandsCosta RicaCroatiaCubaCuraçaoCyprusCzech RepublicCôte d’IvoireDenmarkDiego GarciaDjiboutiDominicaDominican RepublicEcuadorEgyptEl SalvadorEquatorial GuineaEritreaEstoniaEthiopiaFalkland IslandsFaroe IslandsFijiFinlandFranceFrench GuianaFrench PolynesiaFrench Southern TerritoriesGabonGambiaGeorgiaGermanyGhanaGibraltarGreeceGreenlandGrenadaGuadeloupeGuamGuatemalaGuernseyGuineaGuinea-BissauGuyanaHaitiHeard Island and McDonald IslandsHondurasHong Kong SAR ChinaHungaryIcelandIndiaIndonesiaIranIraqIrelandIsle of ManIsraelItalyJamaicaJapanJerseyJordanKazakhstanKenyaKiribatiKosovoKuwaitKyrgyzstanLaosLatviaLebanonLesothoLiberiaLibyaLiechtensteinLithuaniaLuxembourgMacau SAR ChinaMacedoniaMadagascarMalawiMalaysiaMaldivesMaliMaltaMarshall IslandsMartiniqueMauritaniaMauritiusMayotteMexicoMicronesiaMoldovaMonacoMongoliaMontenegroMontserratMoroccoMozambiqueMyanmar [Burma]NamibiaNauruNepalNetherlandsNetherlands AntillesNew CaledoniaNew ZealandNicaraguaNigerNigeriaNiueNorfolk IslandNorthern Mariana IslandsNorth KoreaNorwayOmanOutlying OceaniaPakistanPalauPalestinian TerritoriesPanamaPapua New GuineaParaguayPeruPhilippinesPitcairn IslandsPolandPortugalPuerto RicoQatarRomaniaRussiaRwandaRéunionSaint BarthélemySaint HelenaSaint Kitts and NevisSaint LuciaSaint MartinSaint Pierre and MiquelonSaint Vincent and the GrenadinesSamoaSan MarinoSaudi ArabiaSenegalSerbiaSeychellesSierra LeoneSingaporeSint MaartenSlovakiaSloveniaSolomon IslandsSomaliaSouth AfricaSouth Georgia and the South Sandwich IslandsSouth KoreaSouth SudanSpainSri LankaSudanSurinameSvalbard and Jan MayenSwazilandSwedenSwitzerlandSyriaSão Tomé and PríncipeTaiwanTajikistanTanzaniaThailandTimor-LesteTogoTokelauTongaTrinidad and TobagoTristan da CunhaTunisiaTurkeyTurkmenistanTurks and Caicos IslandsTuvaluU.S. Outlying IslandsU.S. Virgin IslandsUgandaUkraineUnited Arab EmiratesUnited KingdomUnited StatesUruguayUzbekistanVanuatuVatican CityVenezuelaVietnamWallis and FutunaWestern SaharaYemenZambiaZimbabweÅland Islands
Email
Confirm email
My Question
I have read and accept the privacy notice*
I have read and accept the privacy notice*
Ask a question
Post your question - form open message
First name
Last name
Country
CountryAfghanistanAlbaniaAlgeriaAmerican SamoaAndorraAngolaAnguillaAntarcticaAntigua and BarbudaArgentinaArmeniaArubaAscension IslandAustraliaAustriaAzerbaijanBahamasBahrainBangladeshBarbadosBelarusBelgiumBelizeBeninBermudaBhutanBoliviaBosnia and HerzegovinaBotswanaBouvet IslandBrazilBritish Indian Ocean TerritoryBritish Virgin IslandsBruneiBulgariaBurkina FasoBurundiCambodiaCameroonCanadaCanary IslandsCape VerdeCaribbean NetherlandsCayman IslandsCentral African RepublicCeuta and MelillaChadChileChinaChristmas IslandClipperton IslandCocos [Keeling] IslandsColombiaComorosCongo - BrazzavilleCongo - KinshasaCook IslandsCosta RicaCroatiaCubaCuraçaoCyprusCzech RepublicCôte d’IvoireDenmarkDiego GarciaDjiboutiDominicaDominican RepublicEcuadorEgyptEl SalvadorEquatorial GuineaEritreaEstoniaEthiopiaFalkland IslandsFaroe IslandsFijiFinlandFranceFrench GuianaFrench PolynesiaFrench Southern TerritoriesGabonGambiaGeorgiaGermanyGhanaGibraltarGreeceGreenlandGrenadaGuadeloupeGuamGuatemalaGuernseyGuineaGuinea-BissauGuyanaHaitiHeard Island and McDonald IslandsHondurasHong Kong SAR ChinaHungaryIcelandIndiaIndonesiaIranIraqIrelandIsle of ManIsraelItalyJamaicaJapanJerseyJordanKazakhstanKenyaKiribatiKosovoKuwaitKyrgyzstanLaosLatviaLebanonLesothoLiberiaLibyaLiechtensteinLithuaniaLuxembourgMacau SAR ChinaMacedoniaMadagascarMalawiMalaysiaMaldivesMaliMaltaMarshall IslandsMartiniqueMauritaniaMauritiusMayotteMexicoMicronesiaMoldovaMonacoMongoliaMontenegroMontserratMoroccoMozambiqueMyanmar [Burma]NamibiaNauruNepalNetherlandsNetherlands AntillesNew CaledoniaNew ZealandNicaraguaNigerNigeriaNiueNorfolk IslandNorthern Mariana IslandsNorth KoreaNorwayOmanOutlying OceaniaPakistanPalauPalestinian TerritoriesPanamaPapua New GuineaParaguayPeruPhilippinesPitcairn IslandsPolandPortugalPuerto RicoQatarRomaniaRussiaRwandaRéunionSaint BarthélemySaint HelenaSaint Kitts and NevisSaint LuciaSaint MartinSaint Pierre and MiquelonSaint Vincent and the GrenadinesSamoaSan MarinoSaudi ArabiaSenegalSerbiaSeychellesSierra LeoneSingaporeSint MaartenSlovakiaSloveniaSolomon IslandsSomaliaSouth AfricaSouth Georgia and the South Sandwich IslandsSouth KoreaSouth SudanSpainSri LankaSudanSurinameSvalbard and Jan MayenSwazilandSwedenSwitzerlandSyriaSão Tomé and PríncipeTaiwanTajikistanTanzaniaThailandTimor-LesteTogoTokelauTongaTrinidad and TobagoTristan da CunhaTunisiaTurkeyTurkmenistanTurks and Caicos IslandsTuvaluU.S. Outlying IslandsU.S. Virgin IslandsUgandaUkraineUnited Arab EmiratesUnited KingdomUnited StatesUruguayUzbekistanVanuatuVatican CityVenezuelaVietnamWallis and FutunaWestern SaharaYemenZambiaZimbabweÅland Islands
Email
Confirm email
My Question
I have read and accept the privacy notice*
I have read and accept the privacy notice*
Email alert
First Name
Last Name
Career level
Career levelIntership / Thesis workEntry levelMid-senior levelDirectorExecutive
Functional Area
Functional areaGeneral managementOperations - Engineering, Process & TechnologyOperations - LogisticsOperations - Quality control & testingOperations - ProductionsSales ManagementMarketing & Product ManagementHuman ResourcesLegalFinance & ControllingICTPurchaseHSER&DGeneral administration
Country
Country*BelgiumChinaEstoniaFinlandFranceGermanyIndiaMoroccoNorwayPolandRomaniaSpainSwedenThe NetherlandsTurkeyUSAUnited Kingdom
First name
Last name
Email
Confirm email
Street
Nr
Postal Code
City
Country
CountryAfghanistanAlbaniaAlgeriaAmerican SamoaAndorraAngolaAnguillaAntarcticaAntigua and BarbudaArgentinaArmeniaArubaAscension IslandAustraliaAustriaAzerbaijanBahamasBahrainBangladeshBarbadosBelarusBelgiumBelizeBeninBermudaBhutanBoliviaBosnia and HerzegovinaBotswanaBouvet IslandBrazilBritish Indian Ocean TerritoryBritish Virgin IslandsBruneiBulgariaBurkina FasoBurundiCambodiaCameroonCanadaCanary IslandsCape VerdeCaribbean NetherlandsCayman IslandsCentral African RepublicCeuta and MelillaChadChileChinaChristmas IslandClipperton IslandCocos [Keeling] IslandsColombiaComorosCongo - BrazzavilleCongo - KinshasaCook IslandsCosta RicaCroatiaCubaCuraçaoCyprusCzech RepublicCôte d’IvoireDenmarkDiego GarciaDjiboutiDominicaDominican RepublicEcuadorEgyptEl SalvadorEquatorial GuineaEritreaEstoniaEthiopiaFalkland IslandsFaroe IslandsFijiFinlandFranceFrench GuianaFrench PolynesiaFrench Southern TerritoriesGabonGambiaGeorgiaGermanyGhanaGibraltarGreeceGreenlandGrenadaGuadeloupeGuamGuatemalaGuernseyGuineaGuinea-BissauGuyanaHaitiHeard Island and McDonald IslandsHondurasHong Kong SAR ChinaHungaryIcelandIndiaIndonesiaIranIraqIrelandIsle of ManIsraelItalyJamaicaJapanJerseyJordanKazakhstanKenyaKiribatiKosovoKuwaitKyrgyzstanLaosLatviaLebanonLesothoLiberiaLibyaLiechtensteinLithuaniaLuxembourgMacau SAR ChinaMacedoniaMadagascarMalawiMalaysiaMaldivesMaliMaltaMarshall IslandsMartiniqueMauritaniaMauritiusMayotteMexicoMicronesiaMoldovaMonacoMongoliaMontenegroMontserratMoroccoMozambiqueMyanmar [Burma]NamibiaNauruNepalNetherlandsNetherlands AntillesNew CaledoniaNew ZealandNicaraguaNigerNigeriaNiueNorfolk IslandNorthern Mariana IslandsNorth KoreaNorwayOmanOutlying OceaniaPakistanPalauPalestinian TerritoriesPanamaPapua New GuineaParaguayPeruPhilippinesPitcairn IslandsPolandPortugalPuerto RicoQatarRomaniaRussiaRwandaRéunionSaint BarthélemySaint HelenaSaint Kitts and NevisSaint LuciaSaint MartinSaint Pierre and MiquelonSaint Vincent and the GrenadinesSamoaSan MarinoSaudi ArabiaSenegalSerbiaSeychellesSierra LeoneSingaporeSint MaartenSlovakiaSloveniaSolomon IslandsSomaliaSouth AfricaSouth Georgia and the South Sandwich IslandsSouth KoreaSouth SudanSpainSri LankaSudanSurinameSvalbard and Jan MayenSwazilandSwedenSwitzerlandSyriaSão Tomé and PríncipeTaiwanTajikistanTanzaniaThailandTimor-LesteTogoTokelauTongaTrinidad and TobagoTristan da CunhaTunisiaTurkeyTurkmenistanTurks and Caicos IslandsTuvaluU.S. Outlying IslandsU.S. Virgin IslandsUgandaUkraineUnited Arab EmiratesUnited KingdomUnited StatesUruguayUzbekistanVanuatuVatican CityVenezuelaVietnamWallis and FutunaWestern SaharaYemenZambiaZimbabweÅland Islands
Phone
Feel free to add a personal message
Upload your CV*(Word, PDF - max 5 MB)
One file only.5 MB limit.Allowed types: pdf doc docx.
Upload your motivation letter(Word, PDF - max 5 MB)
One file only.5 MB limit.Allowed types: pdf doc docx.
We care about your privacy. That's why we will only use your data to reply to your enquiry. Find out more in our privacy notice to job applicants. At any moment, you can access, modify or have your personal data erased by sending a request to dataprotection@recticel.com
Agree with privacy statement
I have read and accept the privacy notice to job applicants*
